

## **Profile**

Experienced Executive Assistant and Human Resources Specialist.Combined experience in all areas of administrative assistance and HR operations, compensation and benefit administration, employee relations, employee induction/onboarding, compliance, performance management, recruitment, Health and Safety, restructuring and Macedonian Law on labor relations.

## **Employment History**

Human Resources Specialist, Mlekara AD Bitola Joint Stock Company for Dairy Product

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

- Maintaining, preparing and process payroll for organization personnel and preparing MPIN form input
- Handling Recruitment process(drafts, coordinating publishing of job openings, prescreening applications, prepares long/short list of candidates, organizing job interviews and making final decision for selected candidates
- Implementing **new hire orientation** and employee recognition programs.
- Responsible for preparation and administration of specific documentation for Health and Safety (including: Medical checks, incidents at the work place, Certificates for completed HSE trainings
- Preparing HR budget (Forecasting on number of employees, Employee turnover rates, Salary data, Recruitment budget, New benefits programs, Training and development, Payroll costs, Overtime, Incentive compensation...)
- Calculating amounts for payment of sick leaves, vacations, paid leaves and other payroll related documents and tracks of employees absence
- Preparation of the entire documentation for the issuance of a work permit for a Foreigner
- Continuous follow up on Labor Law legislative and Health and Safety regulations and ensuring that all changes are applied
- Reviews training needs, modifies or improves existing programs or develops new training programs to meet those needs.
- Following up the implementation of the performance evaluation procedure
- Preparing various reports and analyses according to the legal reguirements and upon request of the management

Executive Assistant and HR administrator, Mlekara AD Bitola (Joint Stock Company for Dairy Product

JANUARY 2011 - JULY 2018

https://www.crnobelo.com/zivot/kariera/13719-intervju-so-marija-karadzoska-mlekara-ad-

- Assisting the General Manager in all tasks related with internal communication and follow-ups
- Assisting and organize all internal and external events and meetings with external entities
- Scheduling appoitments, organizing meetings, making travel organizations and hotel bookings
- Checking the documents to be signed that they are ready for signing, which are of different levels of confidentiality

**Details** 

Karposh 9/1-3
Bitola, 7000
Macedonia, Republic of
070/370-344
marija.karadzoska@gmail.com

DRIVING LICENSE

В

23.12.1982

## Links

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marija-karadzos

## Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Microsoft Office

**Employee Training** 

**Human Resources** 

**Employee Relations** 

Employee Recruitment & Retention

HR Administration

#### **Hobbies**

Member in a folk dance group Reading books

## Languages

English

Serbian

JANUARY 2010 - APRIL 2010

- Helping users to choose the best products and services for their communication needs
- Presentation of products and services to users and the latest technological advances
- Accession to the sales and service activities with patience, honesty and empathy

## Receptionist, Hotel De Niro, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2003 - AUGUST 2017

- Making and confirming reservations for guests
- Assisting guests with check-in and check-out
- Manage guest bookings and reservations

# **Education**

Bachelor (first cycle), Accounting, finance and auditing, University Kliment Ohridski-Bitola / Faculty of Economics,